yeah gehen in the wake of that paper I
wrote with Kenny I can bring her into
the room where we all met at built or
Birds house and had this little power
and one of the things I said there I'll
say here which is that although we are
sometimes in dialogues like this we are
so fundamentally on the same team and
it's critical to understand how
essential it is we get our acts together
as a team even though we have diverse
perspectives right you have to
understand that we're in the midst of a
compounding kind of meta crisis of the
global level one of the crises is a
crisis of capability which is an
educational crisis and as the situation
gets worse we're going to have
increasingly coercive measures used to
change the nature of human capital right
and the most obvious one in
psychopharmacology right which is an
actual physical intervention into the
central nervous system of over six
million children in the United States
and this is because we have a psychology
that does not understand development
organically or development at all so
there's a way which we are debating but
there's a more much more profound way in
which one of our tasks is to change the
way we think about what it means to
change people's minds and that requires
thinking deeply about developmental
psychology and developmental measurement
and trying to supplant what has become a
human capital management system on a
global scale that is decimating the life
prospects of up and coming generations
and so it's an urge is an urgency and
feel to align and to build a way forward
for human development as a field if only
so that the educational systems of
tomorrow are dignified